The Chimera has multiple attributes.
A head of fire, a body of
earth, and a tail of water.
I'm guessing it'll break
out of the ice pretty soon.
You and I are about to undertake
our first Herculean labor of love.
We'll start with the head.
Your fire alone won't damage it much, so
I'll give you some backup with my water.
Will that be enough?
Even a combined attack will leave us
vulnerable to its water-based tail.
I've got a plan for that.
The plan has already been set in motion.
Are you sure about this?
If we want to be together,
we have to take this risk.
I understand.
But it will take me some time
to prepare for such an endeavor.
I'll buy you all the time you need.
This plan requires me to trust you.
It sure does.
You're having second thoughts
because of Miss Claire. Yes.
Oh, no.
It just...
Time to play some cat-imax,
you big dumb kitty!
That's Ray!
But where's Miss Claire?
Right into our trap!
Now freeze!
Alright, you're up, Ms.
Claire!
Honestly, you act as if it
were just another spell.
As I've told you once before,
this technique is exponentially
more powerful than my others.
If my aim falters in the slightest,
then the spell will strike you as well.
I'm not worried.
I know you can do this, Miss Claire.
Light.
Magic!
Magic! Rain!
I won't be able to stay
by her side anymore.
But at least I know that
Miss Claire won't be alone.
No, ain't you?
I know, no, you have pride
What you want? All you want?
Say that again All I want, only you?
Don't you know what you want?
No, you're not alone.
If you don't even though even though you
don't believe you you're only only this?
You're dead, right?
You're not so happy?
I want to go ahead!
How long you're not?
You're a true self.
Your sending me? It's real! I'm all right.
I'm out!
You're not!
You're fire!
You are too long!
People don't like to see me.
I don't like to see you.
Keep on the feelings!
So let's go!
Now right now!
I'm going to play.
I have a choice.
I'm going to be one thing.
From my heart!
Let's go!
We actually pulled it off, Miss Claire!
Indeed, we're fortunate
things unfolded as they did.
Honestly, what chaos?
Truly impressive.
I mean for a spoiled little
rich girl. Miss Claire!
Prince Dane!
You're bleeding.
Just a scratch.
She barely grazed me.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't the failure,
Prince. Who are you?
Were you the one behind all this?
My initial aim was to eliminate as
many of the nobility as possible,
but this exceeds those aspirations.
Savor your demise.
He got away. I stayed!
Are you alright?
What did he do to you?
Look, his arm.
Prince Tain, stay with us, please!
He's infected with a new type of poison.
Stand back, Miss Claire.
I'll neutralize it.
Looks like he's gonna be all right.
You were able to save him? Yep.
Thank goodness.
It was Cantarella, a deadly poison
from the newer Empire. What?
Is that where the
intruder was from as well?
Yeah, most likely.
Whenever there's a major conflict
in this world, the Noor Empire,
Bauer's sworn enemy, is usually behind it.
They first use Cantorella
in the game's later stages,
and it's up to the heroine
to come up with the antidote.
Thanks to that, I knew how to counteract
it, but still... Rey! I'm here! What?
Fade?
Hey, what the hell happened here?
Cut with a poison blade.
But I neutralized it.
Still, it wouldn't hurt
to take him to a doctor.
I swear...
He just had to charge in by himself.
That idiot.
Looks like they've arrested them already.
Lene...
And just like that, the whole
incident was brought to an end.
The protests have ended, and it seems
the commoner movement is fading out.
We also know that Deed wasn't
responsible for the assault,
and the Nahr Empire was behind
it all from the beginning.
I can't believe we played right into
an enemy nation's hands like that.
Will the entire Oruso family be punished?
Probably.
Even if they were manipulated,
that doesn't change what happened.
They've been relieved of duties
pertaining to Magic Stones,
and they're presently awaiting
the Kingdom's decision.
Decision?
What will happen to them?
What Master Lambert and Lene did
amounts to treason against the Kingdom.
No escaping the death penalty for that.
Oh, I almost forgot to tell you two.
Uh...
Rumor has it that you both
will be receiving a reward.
A reward? Whatever for? Well,
uncovering the mastermind
of an evil plot and
thwarting the plans of
our enemies for starters.
And then there was the part
where Rey saved Thane's life.
It's safe to say you'll be
summoned to the royal palace soon.
Father would like to thank
the both of you personally.
But we let the culprit get away.
Why would... Whoa!
Isn't that something?
We'll gladly take what he has to offer!
Won't we, mister?
What is wrong with you?
Take a breath and listen to me.
I understand.
We shall give it our
very best effort, then.
Will you just sit down?
I can't relax with all that fidgeting.
Sorry, I'm afraid I'm gonna
wrinkle my new outfit.
My lady, thank you for generously
bestowing these sweet thoughts upon me.
Oh, please.
It's not as though I did it for your sake.
I'd be the one facing humiliation if
you showed up looking like a vagrant.
You can act quite all you want, but
we both know it was a gesture of love.
Will you kindly be quiet?
Honestly, it'd actually be rather
striking if you kept your mouth shut.
Huh?
I didn't say a word.
Miss Claire Francois, Miss
Ray Taylor, please follow me.
His Majesty will see you now.
Please, lift your heads.
It has come to my attention
that you two were the ones
responsible for thwarting
the incident at the Academy.
I am also told that you
saved my son's life.
For this, I owe you a great debt.
Name your wish, and it shall be granted.
Your Majesty,
thank you for your generous offer, and
for graciously granting us this audience.
This is entirely up to her.
As much as I'd like to
help, I'm a commoner.
I can't speak directly to the king.
Regarding our reward, there is but
one thing we would like to ask of you.
And what might that be?
A plea, sire.
Here we go, the moment of truth.
I beseech your majesty to
spare the lives of the Orusos!
It was my understanding that the Orasols
were the primary culprits in this matter.
Are you truly suggesting that I
reduce the sentence for their crimes?
Yes, Your Grace.
I humbly request that you show
mercy and grant them a pardon.
Interesting.
Salas, what say you?
It would be difficult.
Ours is a system of reward and punishment.
I see no justification for
commuting their sentence.
This isn't going well.
Your Majesty, I implore you
to think of the Oroso's trade.
In the past, they have
contributed much to our economy,
particularly to the
business of magic stones.
Surely such contributions support
their case for clemency, do they not?
You have a point.
Is it truly infeasible to commute their
sentence in light of their services, Solace?
Indeed, we acknowledge the
contributions you named.
But collusion with a foreign
power and plotting harm
against the kingdom are
crimes of the gravest nature.
Nothing less than execution will suffice.
And so it shall be done.
Please present a different request.
Your Majesty,
if I'm not too late, I'd like to ask
that you consider granting their appeal.
You may approach, Thane.
This turmoil stemmed from unrest
and conflict between the classes.
The commoners rebelled against
what they saw as an injustice,
a wrong done to one of their
own in favor of a noble.
If your majesty does not take
steps to demonstrate equality,
we may face this again in the future.
Hmm.
And you believe that sparing the
Orusos will help improve relations?
Absolutely.
If I may, your majesty, Prince Thane.
There is widespread suspicion
that the Orusos were the
ones who founded the commoner
movement in the first place.
If they are spared, the nobles whose
children were endangered will not accept it.
But people of all backgrounds
contribute to our nation's magic.
Not only nobles, but the common people who
make up the majority of the population.
If you do not wish for your meritocracy
to be called an empty promise,
please reconsider.
I am prepared to make my final judgment.
The Oroso family will be
exiled from this kingdom.
Your Majesty, with all due
- I'll have no dissent.
Apologies.
The details of their banishment
shall be disclosed in due course.
Claire Francois, Ray
Taylor, you are dismissed.
We did it!
Stealing my words, are you?
We just share the same brain cell.
I'm in your head and pretty soon I'm
gonna find my way into your heart.
You will not!
And I share no part of
your demented brain!
Then let's share our love instead!
You just proved my point!
We did it! We did it!
We really, really did it!
Yay, Miss Claire!
There they are.
All of the Oruso's
possessions were confiscated,
and the entire family was
banished to a neighboring land.
So do you think all of them will find
a way to survive out there in the Alps?
I've heard that Bartley, their
family's head, is remarkably competent.
I'm sure they'll secure sufficient
means to put food on the table at least.
But what about Lene and Lambert?
The two of them are being disowned.
And even so, as long as they're
alive, they still have hope.
Lene!
Oh, Ray, Miss Claire.
Someone wanted to come
and say goodbye to you.
I wanted to do nothing of the sort.
You practically dragged me here.
Don't lie.
I could see the longing in your eyes.
Now go on.
You just do your thing
and pretend I'm not here.
Believe me, I constantly try.
Please forgive me for laughing.
It's nice to know some
things haven't changed.
Lene, how are you?
They could easily have executed us.
Considering what we were accused
of, no one would have batted an eye.
But now we have a chance to start over.
Because you two cared enough to intervene.
So thank you for stopping us.
And for speaking to
the king on our behalf.
I'm sorry.
Miss Clara. Time's up.
Lene.
Take these.
Some more recipes.
Just as tasty as the mayonnaise.
For me?
They might help you earn a
few coins out there, you know?
Thank you, Ray.
Thank you both so much. Truly.
I can never repay you.
Bye, Lene. Take care.
Nothing to say?
It's your last chance.
Lene!
I refuse to bid you farewell.
Stay in good health wherever
your path takes you.
I will see you again.
I swear it.
I already told you I don't care.
Now stop prattling and become a horse.
Listen to me, Lene.
You are the servant of Claire Francois,
which makes you the highest-ranked
commoner in this kingdom.
Don't let anyone treat you like that.
Lene, you'll never believe this.
I met the most wonderful,
handsome, charming prince. Lene!
Lene?
Lebe?
She was a good master to you.
Don't say was.
It's not over.
Whatever happens?
Miss Claire will always be my master!
Well, there they go.
Hey, Miss Claire?
What is it?
I'm here if you need a hug, okay?
What a ridiculous suggestion Let's go.
What do you think you're doing?
I will slap you, you impetuous creature!
Don't be afraid to cry. What?
Why would I cry?
I am not so frail the loss of
one servant would make me...
Go ahead.
I can't see your face when
I'm holding you like this.
I told you.
You wanted her to stay, didn't you?
I know.
This world can be so unfair.
Sometimes we can't even stay
with the people we love.
You're incredibly audacious for
a commoner, you realize that.
Yup!
Guess this means you're
gonna punish me for it, huh?
Absolutely not.
You would only consider
it a reward anyway.
You've got me all figured
out, you scrunchies!
Make it true, Sylvie!
All that's enough now is
for us to get married!
That is not happening!
Aw, why not?
I'd be a fun wife!
I hope we see her again.
I'm certain we will, someday.
Oh
And the words that come from
People are mad at all The
combination of feelings With
an open cherry Please repeat
That words that wake
up What are you doing?
What are you getting into your heart?
What you're taking from your heart?
In the moment you feel it's not a mercy!
You're waiting for the truth.
Take care of yourself.
Don't forget to come out!
I'm waiting for that.
You are looking for the passion. Really?
Why are you doing this?
Why do you think this is my one-time girl?
I don't want to see you as a world.
I don't want to meet you.
I don't want to see
you as long as you can!
I don't want to see you
as long as you can! I
don't
want to see
you as long as you can?
will help cheer her up a little.
Oh?
What do you mean?
Don't you know?
She was Claire's first love.